Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Biographical materials, 1946-2016; 1; 6.26 linear feet (15 boxes)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 23, 1970-1975; 5 folders (Box 11, Folder 9-13)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 24, Part 1, 1971-1975; 3 folders (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 24, Part 2, 1970-1979; 4 folders (Box 12, Folder 4-7)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 25, 1970-1976; 3 folders (Box 12, Folder 8-10)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 26, 1970-1979; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 27, 1975-1979; 1 folders (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 28, 1979; 1 folders (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - FBI File: 100-459279, Section 29, 1975-1979; 6 folders (Box 13, Folder 5-10)
  - FBI File: References 106 thru 218, Section 2, 1970-1974; 2 folders (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - FBI File: References 106 thru 218, Section 2, 1970-1974; 2 folders (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - FBI File: References 219 thru 322E, Section 3, 1970-1974; 4 folders (Box 14, Folder 3-6)
  - FBI File: References 323 thru 404, Section 4, 1970-1974; 3 folders (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
  - FBI File: References 405 thru 506E, Section 5, 1970-1975; 3 folders (Box 14, Folder 10-12)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, 1970; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Army Archerd Letter, 1970; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Bank Records, 1970-1971; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Black Panther Party, 1970-1979; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Cleveland Arrest: 11/4/70, 1970; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, FBI: COINTELPRO [Counter Intelligence Program], 1977; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Fonda FBI File:, 1968-1979; 3 folders (Box 15, Folder 7-9)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Fonda FBI File:, 1979; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, "Fonda v. CIA (78-0285)…,", 1971; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Freedom of Information, 2001; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, F.T.A., 1978; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Indochina Peace Campaign (IPC), 1970-1978; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Intelligence Estimates, 1975-1976; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, J. Edgar Hoover, 1970-1972; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Jack Anderson, 1972; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Jane Fonda Affidavit, 1975; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Media Settlement, 1979; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, "Names of Plaintiffs…,", 1974-1978; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Possible Injunction, 1978; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Request Sheets, 2002; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Sedition Investigation, 1972; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Settlement Memo, 1979; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - FBI File: Jane Fonda, Winter Soldier, 1970-1978; 1 folders (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1957-2017; 2; 1.67 linear feet (4 boxes)
  The Correspondence series contains correspondence pertaining to both Jane Fonda's personal, and professional, life. There are two sub-series, General and Subjects. There are oversize materials.
  Both the General and Subjects series are organized first alphabetically, and then chronologically, in each folder. Subjects include family members of Fonda, various friends and celebrities, as well as large sections of fan mail, and correspondence with U.S. Veterans.
  Additional correspondence can be found in Series 3. Professional Activities and Series 4. Writings.
  - General: A-L, 1984-2015; 1 boxes (Box 16, Folder 1-15)
  - General: M-Z, 1969-2016; 1-15 folders (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - General: S, 1998-2015; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - General: Unknown, 2006-2008; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Subjects: 2009 Tony Awards, 2 folders (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
  - Subjects: Iain Armitage, 2016; 1 folders (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Subjects: Mary Catherine Bateson, 2008-2011; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Subjects: Simone Bent, 2007-2008; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Subjects: Patricia Bosworth, 2007-2010; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Subjects: Judith Bruce, 2007-2010; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Subjects: Sandra Bullock, 2014; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Subjects: Jimmy Carter, 1990-2007; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Subjects: Rosalynn Carter, 2006; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Subjects: Caroline Casey, 2007; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Subjects: Margaret Cho, 2010; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Subjects: P. Cleage, 2007-2008; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Subjects: Frances (Pan) Sophia de Villers Brokaw Corria, 1994-2006; 1 folders (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Subjects: Jeff Daniels, 2011; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Subjects: Paz de la Huerta, 2006-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subjects: Eve Ensler, 2001-2011; 4 folders (Box 18, Folder 3-6)
  - Subjects: Jodie Evans, 2006-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Subjects: Sally Field, 2006-2014; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Subjects: Carrie Fisher, 2006; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Subjects: Henry Fonda, 1976-1982; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Subjects: Peter Fonda, 1990-2007; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Subjects: Jane Fonda, 1946-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Subjects: F.T.A., 2005; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Subjects: Troy Garity, 1989-2017; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Subjects: Newt Gingrich, 1999; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Subjects: Sumner Jules Glimcher, 2006; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Subjects: Kathy Griffin, 2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Subjects: Debra W. Haffner, 2006-2007; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Subjects: Joan Halifax, 2008-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Subjects: Tom Hayden, 2008-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Subjects: Lillian Hellman, 1977; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Subjects: Katharine Houghton Hepburn, 1980-1982; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Subjects: Cindy Horn, 2009; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Subjects: Felicity Huffman, 2006-2007; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Subjects: Kelly Irvin, 2007-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subjects: Catherine Keener, 2009-2012; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Subjects: Norman Lear, 2016; 1 folders (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Subjects: Lindsey Lohan, 2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Subjects: Pat Mitchell, 2006-2007; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Subjects: Robin Morgan, 2006-2008; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Subjects: Martina Navratalova, 2006-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Subjects: Rosie O'Donnell, 2006-2010; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Subjects: Jane Olson, 2006; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Subjects: Oprah, 2010-2013; 1 folders (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Subjects: Dolly Parton, 2008-2014; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Subjects: Bonnie Raitt, 1999-2011; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Subjects: Maria Shriver, 2010-2012; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Subjects: Gloria Steinem, 2005-2010; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Subjects: Wanda Sykes, 2006-2009; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Subjects: Sympathy Correspondence for Henry Fonda, 1980-1989; 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Subjects: Toronto Film Festival Controversy, 2008-2009; 2 folders (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Subjects: Ted Turner, 2007-2010; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Subjects: T.V. Guide Readers' Service, A-Z, 1992; 4 folders (Box 19, Folder 11-14)
  - Subjects: Veterans, A-Z, 1999-2009; 6 folders (Box 19, Folder 15-20)
  - Subjects: Veterans, 1999-2009; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Subjects: Mary Luana (Lulu) Williams, 1987-2010; 1 folders (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Professional activities, 1953-2018; 3; 9.59 linear feet (22 boxes)
  Materials related to Fonda's professional life are arranged in four sub-series: Acting, Conferences and Festivals, Interviews, and Organizations and Philanthropy.
  The Acting sub-series is arranged chronologically, and includes scripts, screenplays, clippings, correspondence, notes, musical scores, and contains oversize items. Correspondence related to the Broadway play, 33 Variations, came to the Sophia Smith Collection with water damage. These letters have been photocopied and the originals have been returned to Ms. Fonda.
  The Conferences and Festivals sub-series is arranged alphabetically.
  The Interviews sub-series is arranged alphabetically, and includes transcripts and notes from interviews where Jane Fonda is the interviewer and the interviewee. Some interviews are in French.
  The Organizations and Philanthropy sub-series is arranged alphabetically and includes correspondence, administrative materials, subject files, clippings, posters, resource notebooks, financial statements, and speeches related to the many educational, philanthropic, and humanitarian organizations Fonda has created and/or supported. Some organizations include Fonda, Inc.; the Georgia Campaign for Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention (G-CAPP) (renamed as the Georgia Campaign for Adolescent Power and Potential in 2012), Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), the Fathers' Resource Center; and Women's Media Center (WMC). There are oversize items.
  General
  GCAPP - Elizabeth Appley was Legislative Counsel for GCAPP
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Administrative, 2011; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Advertising, 2011; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Clippings, 2009-2011; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Clippings, 2009-2011; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Correspondence, General, A-Z, 2008-2011; 5 folders (Box 20, Folder 4-9)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Correspondence, General, Unknown, 2009-2011; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Correspondence, Subjects: Moises Kaufman, 2008-2010; 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Program Booklet, 2011; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Scripts: Easter Bonnet Sketch, 22 Apr 2009; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Acting: 33 Variations (2007), Research, 1996; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Acting: 60th Birthday Script, Draft 10, 1997; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Acting: The China Syndrome (1979): correspondence, 1980; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Acting: Fathers and Daughters (2015): correspondence, 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Acting: Georgia Rule (2007), Correspondence, 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Acting: Georgia Rule (2007), Scripts: Production Draft, 2006; 2 folders (Box 20, Folder 20-21)
  - Acting: Grace and Frankie (2015), Correspondence, 2014-2018; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Acting: Grace and Frankie (2015), Notes, 2013-2015; 1 folders (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Acting: Grace and Frankie (2015), Photographs, 2018; 1 folders (1 folder) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Acting: Grapes of Wrath (2010), Advertisement, 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Acting: Grapes of Wrath (2010), Correspondence, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Acting: Grapes of Wrath (2010), Program Booklet, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Acting: Grapes of Wrath (2010), Scripts, Piano/Vocal Score, 2009; 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
  - Acting: Grapes of Wrath (2010), Scripts, Revised Content Script, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Acting: Historia Extraordinarias [Spirits of the Dead] (1968): [advertising poster], 1953; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Acting: Introduction to the Enemy (1974), [advertising poster], 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Acting: Introduction to the Enemy (1974), Organizer's Guide, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Acting: Introduction to the Enemy (1974), Still Negs + Paperwork, 1971; 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Acting: Introduction to the Enemy (1974), Titles and Subtitles, 1970-1975; 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Acting: Invitation to a March (1961): scripts, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Acting: L'Oréal, S.A., "L'Anniversaire 09 06 09,", 2009; 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Acting: L'Oréal, S.A., [Mother's Day Photo Set], 2009; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Acting: Monster-In-Law (2005), Publicity, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Acting: Monster-In-Law (2005), Scripts: "M-I-L", Revised Draft, 2004; 2 folders (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
  - Acting: The Newsroom (2012-2014), Clippings, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Acting: The Newsroom (2012-2014), Correspondence, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Acting: Prime Time Workout & Walkout DVDs (2010), notes, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Acting: Steelyard Blues (1975), correspondence, 1971-1972; 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Acting: This Is Where I Leave You (2014), clippings, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Acting: Youth (2015), correspondence, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Acting: The View (2014), scripts, 1 folders (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Conferences and Festivals: Elle Women in Hollywood, approximately 2017; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Conferences and Festivals: L'Oréal, 2011; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Conferences and Festivals: Oprah's Master Class, 2012; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Conferences and Festivals: Paris Film Festival, 2009-2010; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Conferences and Festivals: UNESCO Charity Gala, 2009; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Interviews: "American Film, Interview with Jane Fonda" [Daniel Petrie, Sr. American Film Institute, Henry Lloyd Master Seminar], 13 Mar 1985; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Interviews: "Changing the Realities of Girls' Lives," Geoffrey Knox, Final Draft, 29 Aug 2000; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Interviews: "Jane Fonda: Taking a Stand Against the Vietnam War," Jodie Singer, 06 Feb 2006; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Interviews: "Le Fou du Roi," Stéphane Guillon, 2005; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Interviews: Mary Catherine Bateson, 2010; 2 folders (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
  - Interviews: Phylippe Geluk, "E'mission de Michele Drucker", 2005; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Interviews: Tape 1 - Budapest-Gyorgy Konrad, 15 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Interviews: Tape 1 - East Berlin, 10 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Interviews: Tape 2 - Budapest Women, 14 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Interviews: Tape 2 - Eva Qwisdorp, 10 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Interviews: Tape 2B - Freimut Duve, 10 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Interviews: Tape 5 - Kurt Masur-Lepizig, 12 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Interviews: Tape 6 - Father Magerius, 12 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Interviews: Tape 6 - Leipzig, 12 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Interviews: Tape 7 - Bitterfield-Hans Zimmerman, 13 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Interviews: Tape 8 - Meeting of New Woman's Forum-East Berlin, 13 Feb 1990; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta History Center, Atlanta's Defining Women, 2003; 1 folders (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), 2000-2004; 2 folders (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), 2000-2004; 2 folders (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Arts Infusion, 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Board, 2002-2004; 2 folders (Box 23, Folder 4-5)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Budget, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), By-Laws, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Director's Report, 2001-2004; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, 2001-2004; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Finance Committee, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Fundraising, 2000-2003; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Governance Committee, c.a. 2001-2004; 2 folders (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Minutes, 2000-2003; 5 folders (Box 23, Folder 14-18)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Outreach, 2002-2003; 1 folders (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Outreach, 2003-2004; 2 folders (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Potential Board Members, 2001-2004; 1 folders (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Program Director, 2004; 1 folders (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Resource Development Committee, 2003; 5 folders (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Schools, 2002-2004; 2 folders (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Strategic Plan, 2002-2005; 1 folders (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Atlanta Partnership for Arts in Learning (APAL), Evaluation, Vision/Mission/Goals, 2002-2005; 1 folders (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Black Lives Matter, 2018; 1 folders (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Cangleska, Inc., correspondence, development plan, and notes, 2002; 4 folders (Box 24, Folder 10-13)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Emma Willard School, 1987-2005; 3 folders (Box 24, Folder 14-16)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fathers' Resource Center, administrative, correspondence, and writings, 1998-2004; 3 folders (Box 24, Folder 17-19)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Flip the 49th!, 2017; 1 folders (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda Family Foundation, 1998-2009; 1 folders (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., 9/11, 2001; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Action Health Incorporated, 1999; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Action Health Incorporated, Secure Their Future…, 1999; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Action Health Incorporated, Caring Parents…, 1999; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Albany, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Athens, GA, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Americus, 1995; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Atlanta Public Schools, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Chatsworth, 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Correspondence, 1997; 1 folders (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Jane Fonda Blog Comments, 2009; 6 folders (Box 25, Folder 10-15)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Jane Fonda Blog Comments, 2009; 4 folders (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Gainesville, 2002; 2 folders (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Garden Homes, 1998; 1 folders (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Generation 2000: Changing Girls' Realities, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Girls' Power Initiative, 2000; 3 folders (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., George Soros, 2003; 1 folders (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Guatemala, 2003; 4 folders (Box 26, Folder 13-16)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Hong Kong, 1994; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., India/Population, 1993-1994; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Insurance Coverage, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Jordan, 1994; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Juarez, 2000-2006; 3 folders (Box 27, Folder 6-8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Mechanicsville, 1993-1997; 2 folders (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Pakistan, 1994; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Plains, GA, 1998; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population and Latin America, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population and Mexico, 1994; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population (Global), 1996-2001; 2 folders (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population (International), 1999; 1 folders (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population Periodicals, 1991-1999; 4 folders (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population Polls, 1994; 2 folders (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Population Services, Inc., 1995-1996; 1 folders (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Pregnancy (General Info), 1998; 1 folders (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Pregnancy Prevention International, 1999; 1 folders (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Pregnancy Prevention for Youth Network (PPFY), 1998-2001; 2 folders (Box 28, Folder 10-11)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Project Preven, 1998-1999; 4 folders (Box 28, Folder 12-15)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Fonda, Inc. Project Prevent, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Rockdale County-Lost Children, 1999; 4 folders (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Savannah, 1995-2000; 3 folders (Box 29, Folder 5-7)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Fonda, Inc., Rising Tide, 2002; 1 folders (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Thomasville Community Resource Center (TCRC), Board Responsibilities, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Thomasville Community Resource Center (TCRC), By Laws, 2003; 1 folders (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Thomasville Community Resource Center (TCRC), Clippings, 2000; 1 folders (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Organizations and Philanthropy: Thomasville Community Resource Center (TCRC), Committees, 2004; 1 folders (Box 29, Folder 12)